Do you like shopping?
你喜欢购物吗？
For shopaholics in the UK, the place to head to used to be the ‘high street’.
对于英国的购物狂来说，过去最值得去的地方是“商业街”（high street）。
This location refers to the streets in the centre of a town where businesses and popular branches of retail chains could be found.
这个地方指的是城镇中心的街道，那里有各类商铺和热门零售连锁店的分店。
It was the place where you could find familiar fashion brands and essential everyday items.
在那里，你能找到熟悉的时尚品牌和必备的日常用品。
But change in our shopping habits has taken its toll on the British high street.
但我们购物习惯的改变，已经给英国商业街带来了沉重打击。
News about shops losing money and shutting is now common.
如今，商店亏损倒闭的新闻屡见不鲜。
Some city-centre department stores have closed and even long-established retailers such as Marks and Spencer have reported profit slumps.
一些市中心的百货公司已经关门，甚至像玛莎百货（Marks and Spencer）这样历史悠久的零售商也报告了利润下滑。
According to the accountancy firm Pricewaterhouse Coopers and the Local Data Company, a record 2,481 shops disappeared from UK high streets last year - up by 40%.
据普华永道会计师事务所和本地数据公司统计，去年英国商业街消失的商店数量达到了创纪录的2481家，同比增长40%。
Even some large warehouse-style stores in out-of-town retail parks, have gone bust and shut up shop.
甚至一些位于城郊零售园区的大型仓储式商店也纷纷破产歇业。
As the BBC’s Emma Simpson writes, things have become a lot harder for traditional retailers in recent years.
正如英国广播公司的艾玛·辛普森所写，近年来传统零售商的日子变得艰难多了。
They have faced rising costs from wages, business rates and the requirement to introduce Europe’s new data law.
他们面临着工资、商业税率上涨以及欧盟新数据法实施带来的成本压力。
But the biggest threat has come from online shopping.
但最大的威胁来自网购。
She says “Consumers now spend one in every five pounds online - and if businesses are seeing 20% fewer sales on the shop floor, as well as their fixed costs rising, then profit margins will be squeezed.”
她说：“现在消费者每花5英镑，就有1英镑是在网上消费的——如果商家的线下销售额下降20%，同时固定成本上升，那么利润率就会受到挤压。”
While some of us like to window shop – browsing for things to buy, only to purchase them online at a discount - the fact is that, overall, shoppers are making fewer visits to high streets.
虽然我们中有些人喜欢只看不买——浏览想买的东西，最后却在网上打折购买——但事实是，总体而言，消费者去商业街的次数越来越少。
Eventually, town centres could become like ghost towns.
最终，城镇中心可能会变成“鬼城”。
If people aren’t out and about shopping, they won’t use other services, like cafes, restaurants and cinemas.
如果人们不外出购物，就不会光顾咖啡馆、餐厅、电影院等其他服务场所。
It also results in job losses.
这也会导致失业。
The British Retail Consortium has already warned that 900,000 UK retail jobs could be lost by 2025.
英国零售协会已经警告，到2025年，英国零售业可能会失去90万个工作岗位。
The high street has also suffered from the advent of big shopping malls, which offer a retail experience under one roof, with free parking, away from the bad weather!
此外，大型购物中心的出现也让商业街雪上加霜——这些购物中心提供一站式购物体验，有免费停车服务，远离恶劣天气！
Meanwhile, back on the high street, some shops still exist.
与此同时，商业街仍有一些商店在苦苦支撑。
Analysts have said it’s those that have moved away from traditional retailing that are surviving.
分析师表示，那些摆脱传统零售模式的店铺才能存活下来。
These include beauty salons, nail bars and independent coffee shops – but are these kinds of shops enough to keep the British high street open for business?
其中包括美容院、美甲店和独立咖啡馆——但这些类型的店铺，是否足以让英国商业街继续运营下去呢？